fixrunner.com 2018-12-04

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: May 31, 2018

FixRunner (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the fixrunner.com website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from fixrunner.com

### Information Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

#### Types of Data Collected

**Personal Data**  
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

·         Email address

·         First name and last name

·         Phone number

·         Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City

·         Cookies and Usage Data

If you are simply browsing and do not register or buy a product or service, you can visit FixRunner.com anonymously.  
Also note that for our free packages you do not need to prove us with your payment information.

**Usage Data**

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

If you are redirected to an offsite payment gateway to complete your payment, we may store this information in a temporary session variable to setup your account when you return to our site.

At checkout, we may also collect your billing address and phone number. This information is used to confirm your credit card. The billing address and phone number are saved by our site to prepopulate the checkout form for future purchases and so we can get in touch with you if needed to discuss your order.

At checkout, we may also collect your credit card number, expiration date, and security code. This information is passed to our payment gateway to process your purchase. The last 4 digits of your credit card number and the expiration date are saved by our site to use for reference and to send you an email if your credit card will expire before the next recurring payment.

When logged in, we use cookies to track some of your activity on our site including logins, visits, and page views.

**Tracking & Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Please note that if you allow Cookies to be enabled, FixRunner.com will make use of these in order to recognize your browser and remember pieces of information for your next visit to the site to make your experience faster and more convenient. This allows us to personalize your time on the FixRunner.com website and recognize your preferences so that we can better meet your needs.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

**Examples of Cookies we use:**

·         Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.

·         Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.

·         Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

### Use of Data

FixRunner uses the collected data for various purposes:

·         To provide and maintain the Service

·         To notify you about changes to our Service

·         To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so

·         To provide customer care and support

·         To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service

·         To monitor the usage of the Service

·         To detect, prevent and address technical issues

The above information provided to us may be used by us to process sales transactions for products or services purchased through Fixrunner.com.  
We may also send you emails from time to time relating to the order that you made through FixRunner.com. These periodic emails will be sent to the email address that you provided for processing your order.  
We may share your information with trusted 3rd parties that assist FixRunner.com is running our website and conducting our business provided that these 3rd parties agree to keep your information confidential.  
We may also provide your information for the purposes of complying with law, enforcing our website’s policies or to protect ours or others’ rights, safety or property.  
Please note that non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Serbia and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Serbia and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

FixRunner will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

**How FixRunner.com does not use this information**

Under no circumstances will FixRunner.com sell, exchange, transfer or share users public or private information with any other company without your consent, unless doing so is expressly for the purpose of delivering to you the product or service that you have purchased through FixRunner.com.

### Disclosure of Data

**Legal Requirements**

FixRunner may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

·         To comply with a legal obligation

·         To protect and defend the rights or property of FixRunner

·         To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service

·         To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public

·         To protect against legal liability

**Security of Data**

FixRunner.com is equipped with a number of security features in order to keep your personal information safe. These measures protect your safety while you are buying a service, registering your information and when you enter login details to access your personal information.  
FixRunner.com is run on a secure server, through which all personal information (including payment details) are sent by SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption to our payment gateway system for maximum safety. These details are only accessible to authorized personnel with the required high level of access rights. Those personnel are also held to this Privacy Policy and its confidentiality requirements.  
Please note that following the completion of a purchase or refund transaction, your private information will not be stored on the FixRunner.com servers.  
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
Service Providers  
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

·  **Google AdWords**

Google AdWords is a web analytics service. You can visit their Privacy Policy page here: https://adwords.google.com/home/

Links to Other Sites  
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

Please note that these 3rd party sites are subject to their own respective privacy policies. FixRunner.com holds no responsibility or liability for the content and activities on these sites.

###  Children’s Privacy  
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Terms of Service**

Please also visit and read our Terms of Service. They clearly lay out the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

###  Consent

By using and visiting FixRunner.com, you consent to our online Privacy Policy.

Contact Us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

· By email: support@fixrunner.com

Address: 6900 Roswell Rd, Atlanta, GA, 30350 &  ISRAEL : 15 Hanashol, Yavne

Tel: +1 (888)-4465559
